{
  "scene_00114_00": {
    "bottle": {
      "19": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The bottle closest to the refrigerator",
          "The bottle closest to the mop",
          "The bottle closest to the gray towel"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What's under the bottle closest to the refrigerator?",
            "answer": "Windowsill",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction is the bottle closest to the mop from the gray towel?",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a window next to the bottle closest to the gray towel?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "22": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The yellow bottle farthest from the refrigerator",
          "The yellow bottle closest to the rice cooker",
          "The yellow bottle closest to the cutting board"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a kettle next to 'the yellow bottle farthest from the refrigerator'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is bigger, 'the yellow bottle closest to the rice cooker' or the steel ball",
            "answer": "Yellow bottle",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the yellow bottle closest to the cutting board' very close to the refrigerator",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "21": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "dark blue bottle",
          "dark blue bottle on the windowsill",
          "dark blue bottle closest to the window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'dark blue bottle'?",
            "answer": "windowsill",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "In which direction of the window is the 'dark blue bottle on the windowsill'?",
            "answer": "beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a plastic bag next to the 'dark blue bottle' closest to the window?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "37": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The water bottle near the kettle",
          "The water bottle far from window",
          "The water bottle on the cabinet"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the water bottle near the kettle'?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the water bottle on the cabinet' close to window?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Where is 'the water bottle far from window'?",
            "answer": "On the cabinet",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "23": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The bottle in the middle of the three closely adjacent bottles",
          "The blue and white striped bottle next to the deep blue bottle",
          "The blue and white striped bottle closest to the cutting board"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What's below 'The bottle in the middle of the three closely adjacent bottles'",
            "answer": "Windowsill",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a refrigerator next to 'The blue and white striped bottle next to the deep blue bottle'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'The blue and white striped bottle closest to the cutting board' far from the rice cooker",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "20": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The yellow bottle closest to the refrigerator",
          "The yellow bottle closest to the mop",
          "The yellow bottle farthest from the cutting board"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Are there other bottles around 'The yellow bottle closest to the refrigerator'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Where is 'The yellow bottle closest to the mop' located?",
            "answer": "On the windowsill above the sink",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'The yellow bottle farthest from the cutting board' on top of the refrigerator?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "bag": {
      "39": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Black plastic bag",
          "Black plastic bag on the floor",
          "Black plastic bag closest to the trash bin"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a kettle next to the 'Black plastic bag'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction on the floor is the 'Black plastic bag' from the trash bin",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'Black plastic bag' closest to the trash bin",
            "answer": "Floor",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "41": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "brown big paper bag",
          "brown paper bag on the floor",
          "paper bag next to the plastic bag"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is the position of the 'brown big paper bag' on the floor",
            "answer": "on top",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a trash bin next to the 'brown paper bag on the floor'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'paper bag next to the plastic bag'?",
            "answer": "brown",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "43": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The paper bag closest to the kettle",
          "The paper bag closest to the stove",
          "The paper bag on the cabinet"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'the paper bag closest to the kettle' red?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the paper bag closest to the stove' on the floor?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a mop next to 'the paper bag closest to the stove'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "cover": {
      "50": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Pot cover on the commode",
          "Pot cover opposite the sink",
          "Pot cover farthest from the mop"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'pot cover on the commode'",
            "answer": "Silver",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What's under the 'pot cover opposite the sink'",
            "answer": "Commode",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a refrigerator next to the 'pot cover farthest from the mop'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "51": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The trash bin lid next to the trash bin",
          "The trash bin lid closest to the refrigerator",
          "The trash bin lid closest to the mop"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the trash bin lid next to the trash bin'?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Where is 'the trash bin lid closest to the refrigerator' relative to the trash bin",
            "answer": "next to",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a door next to 'the trash bin lid closest to the mop'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "cabinet": {
      "28": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "A cabinet with a kettle",
          "The cabinet closest to the trash bin",
          "The cabinet closest to the trash bin lid"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'cabinet with a kettle'?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a sink on the 'cabinet closest to the trash bin'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'cabinet closest to the trash bin lid' next to the door?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "25": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The wall cabinet closest to the yellow towel",
          "The wall cabinet closest to the stove",
          "The wall cabinet closest to the microwave"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'wall cabinet closest to the yellow towel'",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a trash bin under the 'wall cabinet closest to the yellow towel'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the direction of the 'wall cabinet closest to the microwave' from the cutting board",
            "answer": "Above",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "30": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The wall cabinet closest to the refrigerator",
          "The wall cabinet closest to the door",
          "The wall cabinet closest to the mop"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'wall cabinet closest to the refrigerator'",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the position of the 'wall cabinet closest to the door' relative to the refrigerator",
            "answer": "Above",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a stove next to the 'wall cabinet closest to the mop'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "27": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "cabinet under the sink",
          "cabinet under the steel ball",
          "cabinet closest to the water faucet"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What direction is the 'cabinet under the sink' from the steel ball",
            "answer": "below",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'cabinet under the steel ball' blue",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a steel ball on the 'cabinet closest to the water faucet'",
            "answer": "Yes.",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "faucet": {
      "24": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The water faucet next to the steel ball",
          "The water faucet next to the sink",
          "The water faucet closest to the window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'The water faucet next to the steel ball' colorful?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Where is 'The water faucet next to the sink' relative to the steel ball",
            "answer": "Next to",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the floor below 'The water faucet closest to the window'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "kettle": {
      "36": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "black kettle",
          "kettle closest to the stove",
          "kettle opposite the trash can"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'black kettle' under the microwave?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'kettle closest to the stove'?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'kettle opposite the trash can'?",
            "answer": "cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "microwave": {
      "26": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The microwave above the stove",
          "The microwave closest to the kettle",
          "The microwave closest to the rice cooker"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Does the microwave above the stove have a star pattern?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "In what direction of the stove is the microwave closest to the kettle?",
            "answer": "Directly above",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a mop next to the microwave closest to the rice cooker?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "board": {
      "49": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The cutting board closest to the rice maker",
          "The cutting board closest to the microwave",
          "The cutting board farthest from the refrigerator"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What's under the 'cutting board closest to the rice maker'",
            "answer": "Cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What's beside the 'cutting board closest to the microwave' on the direction of the yellow towel",
            "answer": "beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a rice maker beside the 'cutting board farthest from the refrigerator'",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "48": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The cutting board closest to the sink",
          "The cutting board farthest from the rice cooker",
          "The cutting board closest to the steel ball"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the cutting board closest to the sink green?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the cutting board farthest from the rice cooker?",
            "answer": "Cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a cover on the cutting board closest to the steel ball?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "towel": {
      "45": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "white towel",
          "the towel closest to the mop",
          "the towel closest to the fridge"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'white towel' on the floor",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'towel closest to the mop'",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a door next to the 'towel closest to the fridge' ",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "47": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Yellow towel",
          "The towel closest to the stove",
          "The towel closest to the microwave"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'yellow towel' on the floor",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the towel closest to the stove",
            "answer": "Yellow",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Where is the towel closest to the microwave relative to the cutting board",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "steel ball": {
      "34": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The steel ball next to the water faucet",
          "The steel ball above the sink",
          "The steel ball closest to the refrigerator"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'steel ball next to the water faucet' black?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the direction of the 'steel ball above the sink' relative to the water faucet?",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under 'the steel ball closest to the refrigerator'?",
            "answer": "Sink",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "window": {
      "14": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The window next to the door",
          "The window closest to the mop",
          "The window farthest from the rice cooker"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'window next to the door' blue?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction from the door is 'the window closest to the mop'?",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a microwave next to 'the window farthest from the rice cooker'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "17": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The window closest to the sink",
          "The window closest to the steel ball",
          "The window closest to the yellow towel"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the window closest to the sink red?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a microwave next to the window closest to the steel ball?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the window closest to the yellow towel opposite the door?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "door": {
      "13": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White door",
          "Door closest to the refrigerator",
          "Open door"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a window next to the 'White door'",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'Door closest to the refrigerator'",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "In what direction of the stove is the 'Open door'",
            "answer": "Opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "box": {
      "44": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The box closest to the sink",
          "The box closest to the steel ball",
          "The box closest to the faucet"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the box closest to the sink blue?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the box closest to the steel ball?",
            "answer": "Cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Where is the box closest to the faucet in relation to the sink?",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "42": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The box closest to the kettle",
          "The box farthest from the mop",
          "The box closest to the stove"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'box closest to the kettle' blue?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'box farthest from the mop'?",
            "answer": "cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a steel ball on top of the 'box closest to the stove'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "40": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The box next to the black plastic bag",
          "The box closest to the trash bin lid",
          "The box closest to the door"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is under 'the box next to the black plastic bag'",
            "answer": "Floor",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction is 'the box closest to the trash bin lid' from the black trash bag",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a kettle on 'the box closest to the door'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "mop": {
      "16": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The mop closest to the trash bin",
          "The mop next to the refrigerator",
          "The mop closest to the sink"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'mop closest to the trash bin' blue",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a door next to the 'mop next to the refrigerator'",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the position of 'the mop closest to the sink' relative to the stove",
            "answer": "Opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "sink": {
      "33": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The sink closest to the steel ball",
          "The sink closest to the water faucet",
          "The sink in front of window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is 'the sink closest to the steel ball' in front of?",
            "answer": "Window",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a rice cooker next to 'The sink closest to the water faucet'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the object in 'the sink in front of window'?",
            "answer": "Green",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "stove": {
      "29": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Range under the microwave",
          "Range on the floor",
          "The range closest to the kettle"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'range under the microwave' pink?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "In what direction of the microwave is 'the range on the floor'?",
            "answer": "Below",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a box above 'the range closest to the kettle'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "trash can": {
      "38": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Large trash bin",
          "The trash bin opposite the sink",
          "White trash bin"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the large trash bin?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the white trash bin a small one or a large one?",
            "answer": "Large",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the white trash bin close to cutting board?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "light": {
      "46": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The light on the ceiling",
          "The white light",
          "The light above the large trash bin"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'The light on the ceiling' white?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Where is the white light located?",
            "answer": "On the ceiling",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a steel ball next to 'The light above the large trash bin'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "refrigerator": {
      "31": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "mop next to the refrigerator",
          "refrigerator next to the windowsill",
          "refrigerator next to the window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a stove opposite the 'mop next to the refrigerator'",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'refrigerator next to the windowsill' red?",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'refrigerator next to the window'\n",
            "answer": "floor",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "rice cooker": {
      "35": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The rice maker closest to the stove",
          "The rice maker in the corner of the room",
          "The rice maker closest to the cutting board"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'the rice maker closest to the stove' red?",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under 'the rice maker in the corner of the room'?",
            "answer": "cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a refrigerator next to 'the rice maker closest to the cutting board'?",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  },
  "scene_00105_06": {
    "clothes": {
      "37": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The clothes on the chair closest to the monitor",
          "The clothes on the chair closest to the mouse",
          "The clothes on the chair closest to the bed"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'clothes on the chair closest to the monitor' near the bed?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'clothes on the chair closest to the mouse' black?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a monitor next to the 'clothes on the chair closest to the bed'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "42": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Clothes on the chair in the middle of the doorframe",
          "Clothes on the chair under the beam",
          "The dark grey clothes"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color are the 'Clothes on the chair in the middle of the doorframe'",
            "answer": "Dark grey",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Are the 'Clothes on the chair under the beam' very close to the door",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Are the 'Dark grey clothes' on the chair",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "curtain": {
      "40": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Curtain next to the radiator shell",
          "The curtain closer to calendar",
          "The curtain right next to the wall cabinet"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'curtain next to the radiator shell' red",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a radiator shell next to 'the curtain closer to calendar'",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Between the 'curtain right next to the wall cabinet' and the door, which is taller",
            "answer": "curtain",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "41": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The curtain furthest from the radiator shell",
          "The curtain closest to the monitor",
          "The curtain next to the cabinet filled with clothes"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'The curtain furthest from the radiator shell' red?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is taller, 'The curtain closest to the monitor' or the radiator shell?",
            "answer": "curtain",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'The curtain next to the cabinet filled with clothes' far from the TV?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "clock": {
      "16": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The clock on the wall above the TV",
          "The clock next to the calendar",
          "The clock with a blue frame"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the frame of the 'clock on the wall above the TV'?",
            "answer": "Blue",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "In what direction from the TV is the 'clock next to the calendar'?",
            "answer": "Above",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a bed opposite to the 'clock with a blue frame'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "cabinet": {
      "15": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The wall cabinet closest to the clock",
          "The wall cabinet closest to the calendar",
          "The wall cabinet above the radiator shell"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'wall cabinet closest to the clock'?",
            "answer": "Orange",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the position of the 'wall cabinet closest to the calendar' in relation to the radiator shell?",
            "answer": "Above",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a curtain beside the 'wall cabinet above the radiator shell'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "14": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The nightstand closest to the tv",
          "The nightstand closest to the tv box",
          "The nightstand right next to the radiator shell"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'The nightstand closest to the tv' right next to the radiator shell",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Compared to the chair, which is taller, 'The nightstand closest to the tv box'?",
            "answer": "Chair",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'The nightstand right next to the radiator shell' red?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "6": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The cabinet closest to the monitor",
          "The cabinet closest to the keyboard",
          "The cabinet closest to the mouse"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'cabinet closest to the monitor' right next to the small desk?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What's under the 'cabinet closest to the keyboard'?",
            "answer": "Floor",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a telephone on top of the 'cabinet closest to the mouse'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "11": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The cabinet under the TV",
          "The cabinet with the remote control",
          "The cabinet under the tv box"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the cabinet under the TV white?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the cabinet with the remote control right next to the white box?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What material is the cabinet under the tv box made of?",
            "answer": "Wood",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "23": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The nightstand closest to the door",
          "The nightstand closest to the bed",
          "The nightstand closest to the bag"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'The nightstand closest to the door' mahogany colored?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under 'The nightstand closest to the bed'?",
            "answer": "floor",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a green plant next to 'The nightstand closest to the bag'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "radiator shell": {
      "33": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Rectangular radiator shell",
          "Radiator shell under the wall cabinet",
          "Orange-yellow radiator shell"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'rectangular radiator shell'?",
            "answer": "Orange-yellow",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a bed next to the 'radiator shell under the wall cabinet'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Who is taller, the 'orange-yellow radiator shell' or the nightstand right next to it?",
            "answer": "Radiator shell",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "box": {
      "13": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White box",
          "The box closest to the TV",
          "The box closest to the door"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there anything inside the 'white box'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'box closest to the TV' pink?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is bigger, the 'box closest to the door' or the bag?",
            "answer": "box",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "30": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "light brown box",
          "the box under the small desk",
          "the box farthest from the TV"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'light brown box' right next to the radiator shell",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'box under the small desk'",
            "answer": "light brown",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What's under the 'box farthest from the TV'",
            "answer": "under the small desk",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "chair": {
      "34": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Chair with a pillow",
          "Chair right next to the radiator shell",
          "Chair closest to the clock"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'Chair with a pillow'?",
            "answer": "Blue",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What item is on the 'Chair right next to the radiator shell'?",
            "answer": "Pillow",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'Chair closest to the clock' right next to the TV?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "38": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The chair right next to the bed",
          "The chair placed at the corner between the small desk and the end of the bed",
          "The chair closest to the keyboard"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is placed on 'The chair right next to the bed'",
            "answer": "Clothes",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is 'The chair placed at the corner between the small desk and the end of the bed'",
            "answer": "Blue",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is closer to 'The chair closest to the keyboard', door or TV",
            "answer": "TV",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "39": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The chair between the door frames",
          "The chair closest to the radiator shell with clothes on it",
          "The chair right below the beam"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is on the 'The chair between the door frames'",
            "answer": "Clothes",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'The chair closest to the radiator shell with clothes on it' pink?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'The chair right below the beam' close to the door frame?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "pillow": {
      "31": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The white and blue striped pillow on the bed",
          "The pillow with white and blue stripes next to the bag",
          "The pillow with white and blue stripes right next to the head of the bed"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a bag next to the 'white and blue striped pillow on the bed'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What's under the 'pillow with white and blue stripes next to the bag'?",
            "answer": "Bed",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'pillow with white and blue stripes right next to the head of the bed' square?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "19": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "red and white striped pillow",
          "the pillow closest to the telephone",
          "the pillow closest to the door"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a bag next to the red and white striped pillow?",
            "answer": "Yes.",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the pillow closest to the telephone blue?",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the pillow closest to the door placed on?",
            "answer": "bed",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "36": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The pillow closest to the monitor",
          "The pillow closest to the mouse",
          "The pillow closest to the keyboard"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a quilt beside the pillow closest to the monitor",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the direction of the pillow closest to the mouse in relation to the TV",
            "answer": "Opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the pillow closest to the keyboard",
            "answer": "bed",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "35": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The pillow closest to the radiator shell",
          "The pillow closest to the calendar",
          "The pillow closest to the clock"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the pillow closest to the radiator shell pink?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a radiator shell near the pillow closest to the calendar?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What's under the pillow closest to the clock?",
            "answer": "chair",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "table": {
      "47": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The desk closest to the window",
          "The desk on the balcony",
          "The desk closest to the black chair"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the desk closest to the window'?",
            "answer": "Yellow",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is closer to the door frame, 'the desk on the balcony' or the window?",
            "answer": "desk",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a telephone on 'the desk closest to the black chair'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "29": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Desk right next to the bed",
          "Desk with a mouse on it",
          "Desk with a monitor on it"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'Desk right next to the bed' blue?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the position of the 'Desk with a mouse on it' relative to the monitor?",
            "answer": "Below",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is farther from the TV, the 'Desk with a monitor on it' or the TV box?",
            "answer": "Desk with a monitor on it",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "speaker": {
      "26": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Light yellow speaker",
          "Speaker on the small desk",
          "Speaker next to the keyboard"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What's under 'Light yellow speaker'",
            "answer": "Small desk",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a mouse next to 'Speaker on the small desk'",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'Speaker next to the keyboard' black",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "quilt": {
      "21": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The quilt farthest from the keyboard",
          "The quilt farthest from the monitor",
          "The quilt closest to the bag"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What's under 'The quilt farthest from the keyboard'",
            "answer": "bed",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a bag next to 'The quilt farthest from the monitor'",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'The quilt closest to the bag' patterned",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "20": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The light blue quilt at the end of the bed",
          "The light blue quilt closest to the speaker",
          "The light blue quilt closest to the keyboard"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What's under 'The light blue quilt at the end of the bed'",
            "answer": "Quilt",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'The light blue quilt closest to the speaker' placed on a chair",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a bag next to 'The light blue quilt closest to the keyboard'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "mouse": {
      "28": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Mouse next to the keyboard",
          "Mouse next to the monitor",
          "Mouse next to the speaker"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'Mouse next to the keyboard' next to the monitor",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is bigger, the 'Mouse next to the monitor' or the speaker",
            "answer": "Speaker",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'Mouse next to the speaker' red",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "monitor": {
      "25": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "monitor next to the mouse",
          "monitor next to the keyboard",
          "monitor next to the bed"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the screen of the 'monitor next to the mouse'?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'monitor next to the keyboard' close to the bed?",
            "answer": "Close",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'monitor next to the bed'?",
            "answer": "desk",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "tv": {
      "9": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The TV below the calendar diagonally",
          "The black TV",
          "The TV next to the TV box"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'TV below the calendar diagonally'",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a window opposite the 'black TV'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'TV next to the TV box'",
            "answer": "Cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "door": {
      "4": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "the door next to the telephone",
          "yellow door",
          "the door next to the white box"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'door next to the telephone' close to the white box",
            "answer": "Close",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a clock above the 'yellow door'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'door next to the white box'",
            "answer": "Yellow",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "telephone": {
      "24": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Telephone on the nightstand",
          "Telephone next to the door",
          "Black telephone"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'Telephone on the nightstand'?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a small desk under the 'Telephone next to the door'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'Black telephone' close to the door?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "tv box": {
      "12": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The TV box next to the TV",
          "The light gray TV box",
          "The rectangular TV box"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'TV box next to the TV' red?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'light gray TV box' rectangular?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'rectangular TV box'?",
            "answer": "cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "window": {
      "49": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The window next to the black chair",
          "The window above the orange-yellow wall",
          "The glass window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the frame of the 'window next to the black chair' pink?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'window above the orange-yellow wall' next to the black chair?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'glass window' opened or closed?",
            "answer": "Closed",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "bed": {
      "18": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Bed with a bag",
          "Bed with a quilt",
          "Bed next to the monitor"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'Bed with a bag'?",
            "answer": "Brown",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a bag on the 'Bed with a quilt'?",
            "answer": "Yes.",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'Bed next to the monitor' right next to the wall cabinet?",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "calendar": {
      "17": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Calendar right next to the clock",
          "Calendar hanging on the wall",
          "Rectangular calendar"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Does the 'Calendar right next to the clock' have a large tree pattern?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What shape is the 'Calendar hanging on the wall'?",
            "answer": "Rectangular",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'Rectangular calendar' right next to the clock?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "keyboard": {
      "27": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "keyboard next to the mouse",
          "black keyboard",
          "keyboard next to the monitor"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'keyboard next to the mouse'?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a telephone next to the 'black keyboard'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a desk under the 'keyboard next to the monitor'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "bag": {
      "32": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "green bag",
          "bag on the bed",
          "bag next to the striped quilt"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Which is smaller when comparing the 'green bag' with the red and white striped pillow",
            "answer": "bag",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'bag on the bed'",
            "answer": "green",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a pillow right next to the 'bag next to the striped quilt'",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  },
  "scene_00109_00": {
    "chair": {
      "13": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Chair with four pillows",
          "Chair next to an empty chair",
          "Chair with a yellow pillow"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the \"Chair with four pillows\"?",
            "answer": "Grey",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the \"Chair next to an empty chair\" right next to the windowsill?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a suitcase next to the \"Chair with a yellow pillow\"?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "12": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The chair furthest from the speaker with no pillow on it",
          "The chair with no pillow",
          "The chair closest to the small window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a couch next to the chair furthest from the speaker with no pillow on it",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the chair with no pillow",
            "answer": "Grey",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the chair closest to the small window right next to the TV",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "15": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The chair closest to the green suitcase",
          "The chair closest to the wood fence",
          "The chair closest to the blue painting"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the chair closest to the green suitcase'",
            "answer": "Gray",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is bigger, 'the chair closest to the wood fence' or the green suitcase",
            "answer": "Chair",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a TV next to 'the chair closest to the blue painting'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "speaker": {
      "20": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Speaker on the table",
          "The black speaker",
          "The round speaker"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'Speaker on the table'",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What shape is the 'black speaker'",
            "answer": "Round",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'round speaker' right next to the wood fence",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "box": {
      "24": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "green suitcase",
          "green suitcase next to the couch",
          "green suitcase furthest from the window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'green suitcase' upright?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a TV next to the 'green suitcase next to the couch'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is closer to the speaker, the 'green suitcase furthest from the window' or the blue painting?",
            "answer": "green suitcase",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "23": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Black suitcase right next to the pillar",
          "Black suitcase farthest from the windowsill",
          "Black suitcase closest to the speaker"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there another suitcase next to the 'Black suitcase right next to the pillar'",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'Black suitcase farthest from the windowsill' close to the tv",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is smaller, the 'Black suitcase closest to the speaker' or the silver-white suitcase next to it",
            "answer": "Black suitcase",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "21": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The suitcase on the table",
          "The flat suitcase",
          "The black suitcase farthest from the speaker"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'suitcase on the table' blue?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under 'the flat suitcase'?",
            "answer": "Table",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is closer to the TV, the 'black suitcase farthest from the speaker' or the wood fence?",
            "answer": "Suitcase",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "22": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Silver-white suitcase",
          "The silver-white suitcase opposite the TV",
          "The silver-white suitcase closest to the pillar"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there any other suitcase next to the 'silver-white suitcase'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'silver-white suitcase' opposite the TV right next to a green suitcase?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is a bit farther from the TV stand, the 'silver-white suitcase' closest to the pillar or the speaker?",
            "answer": "Silver-white suitcase",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "sofa cushion": {
      "32": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The sofa cushion furthest from the window",
          "The sofa cushion closest to the blue painting",
          "The sofa cushion furthest from the windowsill"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a silver-white suitcase next to the sofa cushion that is furthest from the window?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the sofa cushion closest to the blue painting?",
            "answer": "Grey",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the sofa cushion furthest from the windowsill close to the wood fence?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "29": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The sofa cushion closest to the windowsill",
          "The sofa cushion closest to the large window",
          "The sofa cushion farthest from the speaker"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a suitcase next to the 'sofa cushion closest to the windowsill'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'sofa cushion closest to the large window'",
            "answer": "Gray",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'sofa cushion farthest from the speaker' right next to a pillow",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "tv": {
      "10": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "black TV",
          "TV hanging on the TV stand",
          "TV opposite the silver suitcase"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Does the 'black TV' have an image pattern?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'TV hanging on the TV stand'?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'TV opposite the silver suitcase' hanging above the TV stand?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "fence": {
      "4": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Natural colored wood fence",
          "Wood fence next to the pillar",
          "Wood fence behind the sofa"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "The natural colored wood fence and the windowsill, which is closer to the speaker?",
            "answer": "The natural colored wood fence",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a window next to 'the wood fence next to the pillar'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the wood fence behind the sofa'?",
            "answer": "Natural colored",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "table": {
      "19": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "the table with the speaker",
          "the table farthest from the windowsill",
          "the table farthest from the window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the table with the speaker'?",
            "answer": "Yellow",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a suitcase on 'the table farthest from the windowsill'?",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is on 'the table farthest from the window'?",
            "answer": "speaker",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "18": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The table closest to the wood fence",
          "The table with the suitcase on it",
          "The table closest to the windowsill"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'table closest to the wood fence'?",
            "answer": "Yellow",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'table with the suitcase on it' right next to the wall?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What item is on the 'table closest to the windowsill'?",
            "answer": "suitcase",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "pillow": {
      "27": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The yellow pillow on the sofa closest to the windowsill",
          "The yellow pillow on the sofa farthest from the speaker",
          "The yellow pillow on the sofa closest to the large window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'yellow pillow on the sofa closest to the windowsill' close to the wood fence",
            "answer": "Yes.",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a painting next to the 'yellow pillow on the sofa farthest from the speaker'",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'yellow pillow on the sofa closest to the windowsill' rectangular?",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "36": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The first yellow pillow on the chair closest to the window",
          "The first yellow pillow on the chair farthest from the speaker",
          "The first yellow pillow on the chair closest to the windowsill"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is the direction of 'the first yellow pillow on the chair closest to the window' relative to the windowsill",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the first yellow pillow on the chair farthest from the speaker' square?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a TV next to 'the first yellow pillow on the chair farthest from the speaker'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "30": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The pure black pillow closest to the pillar",
          "The pure black pillow closest to the wood fence",
          "The pure black pillow on the couch"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What's under 'The pure black pillow closest to the pillar'",
            "answer": "Couch",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a suitcase near 'The pure black pillow closest to the wood fence'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'The pure black pillow on the couch' close to the TV?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "37": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The second pillow from the top on the chair furthest from the big backpack",
          "The second pillow from the top on the chair furthest from the speaker",
          "The second pillow from the top on the chair closest to the windowsill"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'The second pillow from the top on the chair furthest from the big backpack' blue?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is smaller, the 'The second pillow from the top on the chair furthest from the speaker' or the green suitcase?",
            "answer": "Pillow",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there another chair next to 'The second pillow from the top on the chair closest to the windowsill'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "46": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The outermost pillow on the chair closest to the green suitcase",
          "The outermost pillow on the chair closest to the small backpack",
          "The outermost pillow on the chair closest to the blue painting"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a bird pattern on 'The outermost pillow on the chair closest to the green suitcase'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What shape is 'The outermost pillow on the chair closest to the small backpack'",
            "answer": "Rectangular",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a green suitcase next to 'The outermost pillow on the chair closest to the blue painting'",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "couch": {
      "17": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Sofa with a backpack",
          "The sofa closest to the speaker",
          "The sofa closest to the green suitcase"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the sofa with a backpack",
            "answer": "Light brown",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a backpack on the sofa closest to the speaker",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the sofa closest to the green suitcase under the windowsill",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "16": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "a sofa without a backpack",
          "a sofa with two pillows",
          "the sofa closest to the window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a speaker next to the 'sofa without a backpack'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'sofa with two pillows'?",
            "answer": "Gray",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'sofa closest to the window' near the wood fence?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "picture": {
      "44": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The painting closest to the windowsill",
          "The painting closest to the window",
          "The painting furthest from the speaker"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'The painting closest to the windowsill' very close to the sofa with the yellow cushions",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the frame of 'The painting closest to the window'",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a TV next to 'The painting furthest from the speaker'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "9": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Blue painting",
          "The blue painting farthest from the window",
          "The blue painting closest to the green suitcase"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the frame of the 'blue painting'",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the blue painting farthest from the window' very close to the speaker",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there another painting next to 'the blue painting closest to the green suitcase'",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "8": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The painting closest to the chair with two pillows",
          "The painting closest to the table with a speaker",
          "The painting closest to the speaker"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a TV next to the painting closest to the chair with two pillows",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is bigger, the painting closest to the table with a speaker or the green suitcase",
            "answer": "Painting",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the frame of the painting closest to the speaker",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "bag": {
      "26": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The smallest backpack",
          "The smallest backpack on the couch",
          "The backpack farthest from the pillar"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the smallest backpack'",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the position of 'the smallest backpack on the couch' relative to the speaker",
            "answer": "Opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under 'the backpack farthest from the pillar'",
            "answer": "couch",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "25": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The backpack closest to the silver suitcase",
          "The biggest backpack on the couch",
          "The backpack closest to the windowsill"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the backpack closest to the silver suitcase blue?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the biggest backpack on the couch right next to the gray and white striped cushion?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is below the backpack closest to the windowsill?",
            "answer": "Couch",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "cabinet": {
      "6": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "A tv cabinet with a TV mounted on it",
          "A tv cabinet right next to the largest wall",
          "A golden tv cabinet"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the tv cabinet with a TV mounted on it golden in color?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Between the tv cabinet right next to the largest wall and the blue painting, which is taller?",
            "answer": "The tv cabinet right next to the largest wall",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the golden tv cabinet right next to the wood fence?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "window": {
      "42": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The largest window",
          "The window closest to the striped painting",
          "The window closest to the chair with a yellow pillow"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Which is further from the TV, 'The largest window' or the speaker?",
            "answer": "The largest window",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a chair next to 'the window closest to the striped painting'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Does 'the window closest to the chair with a yellow pillow' have a flower pattern on it?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  },
  "scene_00106_05": {
    "cabinet": {
      "1": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The cabinet next to the mirror",
          "The cabinet closest to the colorful box",
          "The cabinet next to the orange chair"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a suitcase on the cabinet next to the mirror",
            "answer": "Yes.",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the cabinet closest to the colorful box black?",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction is the cabinet next to the orange chair in relation to the bed",
            "answer": "Opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "17": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "A cabinet with a basket",
          "A yellow cabinet right next to a blue chair",
          "A yellow cabinet closest to the bed"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the cabinet with a basket?",
            "answer": "Yellow",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the yellow cabinet right next to a blue chair?",
            "answer": "Floor",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a basket on the yellow cabinet closest to the bed?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "22": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "A cabinet with a clock",
          "The cabinet farthest from the curtain",
          "The cabinet farthest from the window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the cabinet with a clock blue?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction is the cabinet that is farthest from the curtain relative to the curtain box?",
            "answer": "Opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the cabinet that is farthest from the window?",
            "answer": "Floor",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "40": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The cabinet closest to the curtain",
          "The cabinet with white drawers",
          "The cabinet with white drawers closest to the window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What's the color of the drawers of the 'cabinet closest to the curtain'",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'cabinet with white drawers' right next to the bed",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a door next to the 'cabinet with white drawers closest to the window'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "19": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Yellow short commode",
          "The yellow short commode farthest from the window",
          "The yellow short commode farthest from the woodcarving"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'Yellow short commode' right next to the door",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there another commode next to 'The yellow short commode farthest from the window'",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is taller, 'The yellow short commode farthest from the woodcarving' or the bed",
            "answer": "Yellow short commode",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "pillow": {
      "37": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The pillow closest to the basket",
          "The pillow on the chair opposite the door",
          "The pillow on the chair with pink and yellow patterns"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Does the 'pillow closest to the basket' have a pattern",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a box next to the 'pillow on the chair opposite the door'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which is bigger, the 'pillow on the chair with pink and yellow patterns' or the clock",
            "answer": "Pillow",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "32": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The pillow closest to the mirror",
          "The pillow closest to the monitor",
          "The pillow closest to the paper"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the pillow closest to the mirror blue?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What's under the pillow closest to the monitor?",
            "answer": "chair",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a chair under the pillow closest to the paper?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "39": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "A pillow with a blue dot pattern on a white background",
          "The pillow on the bed",
          "The pillow closest to the curtain"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "In which direction is the 'pillow with a blue dot pattern on a white background' from the curtain",
            "answer": "below",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'pillow on the bed' red?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is below the 'pillow closest to the curtain'?",
            "answer": "bed",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "basket": {
      "18": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Rectangular basket",
          "Yellow basket",
          "Basket near the bed"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the rectangular basket?",
            "answer": "Yellow",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What shape is the yellow basket?",
            "answer": "Rectangular",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'Basket near the bed'?",
            "answer": "Cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "chair": {
      "10": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The chair closest to the windowsill",
          "The chair closest to the window",
          "The chair closest to the curtain"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the chair closest to the windowsill black?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What position is the chair closest to the window in relation to the woodcarving?",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a door next to the chair closest to the curtain?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "38": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The chair closest to the bed",
          "The chair closest to the basket",
          "The blue chair farthest from the paper"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What's on 'The chair closest to the bed'",
            "answer": "pillow",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is 'The chair closest to the basket'",
            "answer": "Blue",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "In what direction of the bed is 'The blue chair farthest from the paper'",
            "answer": "beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "33": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The chair closest to the pc",
          "The chair closest to the paper",
          "The chair right next to the desk"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is on the chair closest to the pc",
            "answer": "pillow",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the chair closest to the paper right next to the desk",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the chair right next to the desk purely black",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "box": {
      "29": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The suitcase closest to the window",
          "The suitcase closest to the curtain box",
          "The suitcase farthest from the door"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'suitcase closest to the window'?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction from the bed is the 'suitcase closest to the curtain box' located?",
            "answer": "Opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a telephone on top of the 'suitcase farthest from the door'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "36": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The box closest to the bed",
          "The box closest to the door",
          "The box closest to the monitor"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'The box closest to the bed' black?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What's under 'The box closest to the door'?",
            "answer": "floor",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a table next to 'The box closest to the monitor'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "26": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The black suitcase directly below the colorful box",
          "The black suitcase closest to the mirror",
          "The black suitcase closest to the personal computer"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a red heart pattern on the 'Black suitcase directly below the colorful box'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the direction of the 'Black suitcase closest to the mirror' relative to the colorful box?",
            "answer": "Below",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a cabinet under the 'Black suitcase closest to the personal computer'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "25": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "suitcase closest to the mirror",
          "suitcase closest to the clock",
          "red suitcase farthest from the window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the suitcase closest to the mirror?",
            "answer": "Red",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is underneath the suitcase closest to the clock?",
            "answer": "Cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a basket next to the red suitcase farthest from the window?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "30": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "colorful boxes",
          "the colorful boxes on top of the black suitcase",
          "the colorful boxes beside the wall"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'colorful boxes'",
            "answer": "suitcase",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "In which direction of the wall is the 'colorful boxes' on top of the black suitcase",
            "answer": "beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a pillow on top of the 'colorful boxes' beside the wall",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "31": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White box",
          "The white box closest to the mirror",
          "The white box closest to the curtain box"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is the position of the 'White box' relative to the red suitcase",
            "answer": "On top",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a pc next to the 'White box' closest to the mirror",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'White box' closest to the curtain box next to the door",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "table": {
      "5": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The table closest to the curtain box",
          "The table closest to the window",
          "The table furthest from the pen"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the table closest to the curtain box black?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction is the table closest to the window from the bed?",
            "answer": "Opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a curtain on the table furthest from the pen?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "35": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The desk with a monitor",
          "The desk with paper",
          "The desk farthest from the window"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What's the direction of the pen relative to 'the desk with a monitor'?",
            "answer": "Below",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a pillow on 'the desk with paper'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What's under 'the desk farthest from the window'?",
            "answer": "Floor",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "mirror": {
      "3": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The mirror closest to the monitor",
          "The mirror closest to the computer",
          "The mirror opposite the bed"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Does the 'mirror closest to the monitor' have a frame?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the position of the 'mirror closest to the computer' relative to the basket",
            "answer": "opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a telephone next to the 'mirror closest to the monitor'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "bed": {
      "12": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "A bed with pillows on it",
          "A bed with a white headboard",
          "A bed below the curtain"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'bed with pillows on it' right next to the curtain?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'bed with a white headboard' close to the mirror?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the headboard of the 'bed below the curtain'?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "windowsill": {
      "42": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "the windowsill beside the window",
          "the windowsill closest to the curtain",
          "the windowsill above the woodcarving"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is the direction of 'the windowsill beside the window' from the door",
            "answer": "Opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under 'the windowsill closest to the curtain'",
            "answer": "woodcarving",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the windowsill above the woodcarving' pink",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "paper": {
      "8": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "white paper",
          "paper under the pen",
          "the paper closest to the monitor"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "The position of the 'white paper' related to the pen?",
            "answer": "under",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'paper under the pen'?",
            "answer": "white",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a bed next to the 'paper closest to the monitor'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "clock": {
      "21": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White clock",
          "The clock hanging on the largest cabinet",
          "The clock closest to the door"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a bed next to the 'White clock'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the clock hanging on the largest cabinet'",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "In what direction of the window is 'the clock closest to the door'",
            "answer": "Opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "telephone": {
      "4": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The telephone closest to the mirror",
          "The telephone farthest from the door",
          "The telephone farthest from the personal computer"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'telephone closest to the mirror' yellow?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction from the mirror is the 'telephone farthest from the door'?",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a window beside the 'telephone farthest from the personal computer'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "34": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White cellphone",
          "cellphone next to the monitor",
          "cellphone closest to the mirror"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Where is the 'White cellphone' in relation to the monitor",
            "answer": "Next to",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'cellphone next to the monitor'",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a bed next to the 'cellphone closest to the mirror'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "window": {
      "13": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "window next to the windowsill",
          "window opposite the door",
          "window next to the curtain"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there paper next to the window by the windowsill?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the window opposite the door?",
            "answer": "windowsill",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction from the door is the window next to the curtain?",
            "answer": "opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "door": {
      "20": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Yellow door",
          "The door closest to the clock",
          "The door closest to the basket"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is the position of the 'yellow door' relative to the window",
            "answer": "Opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the color of 'the door closest to the clock'",
            "answer": "Yellow",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a telephone next to 'the door closest to the basket'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "monitor": {
      "9": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Black monitor",
          "Monitor next to paper",
          "Monitor on the desk"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a cabinet under the 'Black monitor'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'Monitor next to paper'?",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'Monitor on the desk' right next to the bed?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "curtain": {
      "14": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The curtain closest to the windowsill",
          "The curtain closest to the window",
          "The curtain farthest from the door"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'The curtain closest to the windowsill' yellow?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction is 'The curtain closest to the window' from the windowsill?",
            "answer": "Besides",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a clock beside 'The curtain farthest from the door'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "wood carving": {
      "41": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "woodcarving under the windowsill",
          "woodcarving closest to the window",
          "woodcarving closest to the curtain"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a telephone on the woodcarving under the windowsill",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction of the windowsill is the woodcarving closest to the window",
            "answer": "below",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the woodcarving closest to the curtain blue",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "computer": {
      "6": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The PC closest to the cellphone",
          "The PC closest to the monitor",
          "The PC closest to the mirror"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'PC closest to the cellphone'",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What's under the 'PC closest to the monitor'",
            "answer": "Floor",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a curtain next to the 'PC closest to the mirror'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  },
  "scene_00116_03": {
    "toilet paper": {
      "20": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White toilet paper",
          "Toilet paper placed inside the wall cabinet",
          "The toilet paper closest to the stove"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is the position of the 'White toilet paper' in the wall cabinet",
            "answer": "inside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the toilet paper placed inside the wall cabinet",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a door opposite the 'toilet paper closest to the stove'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "pot": {
      "30": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "the pot in the sink",
          "the pot next to the sponge",
          "the pot closest to the books"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'the pot in the sink' close to the sponge",
            "answer": "yes",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Where is 'the pot next to the sponge'?",
            "answer": "In the sink",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a range hood above 'the pot closest to the books'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "23": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "On the stove, the large pot",
          "The large pot nearest to the trash bin",
          "The large pot nearest to the cutting board"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'the large pot on the stove' in red color?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What's under 'the large pot nearest to the trash bin'?",
            "answer": "Stove",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a door next to 'the large pot nearest to the cutting board'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "24": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Black pot",
          "The pot closest to the trash bin",
          "The small pot above the stove"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What's under the 'Black pot'",
            "answer": "Stove",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is 'The pot closest to the trash bin'",
            "answer": "Black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a sink next to 'The small pot above the stove'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "bottle": {
      "35": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The bottle closest to the toilet paper",
          "The bottle with the orange cap",
          "The bottle closest to the trash can"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the cap of 'the bottle closest to the toilet paper'?",
            "answer": "Orange",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What's under 'the bottle with the orange cap'?",
            "answer": "cabinet",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a cutting board next to 'the bottle closest to the trash can'?",
            "answer": "Yes.",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "31": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White bottle",
          "The bottle closest to the refrigerator",
          "The bottle closest to the book"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a door next to the 'White bottle'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is 'The bottle closest to the refrigerator'?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under 'The bottle closest to the book'?",
            "answer": "cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "sponge": {
      "33": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The sponge next to the sink",
          "Yellow sponge",
          "The sponge near a pot"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'sponge next to the sink'",
            "answer": "Yellow",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Where is the yellow sponge in relation to the sink?",
            "answer": "Next to",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a pot near the yellow sponge?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "cabinet": {
      "15": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The wall cabinet right above the sink",
          "The wall cabinet closest to the books",
          "The wall cabinet above the kettle"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'The wall cabinet right above the sink' red?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "In what direction from the sink is 'The wall cabinet closest to the books'?",
            "answer": "Directly above",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there toilet paper inside 'The wall cabinet above the kettle'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "18": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The cabinet with the cutting board",
          "The cabinet closest to the bifold door",
          "The cabinet closest to the trash bin"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'cabinet with the cutting board'?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Which side of the trash bin is the 'cabinet closest to the bifold door' located?",
            "answer": "beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a refrigerator next to the 'cabinet closest to the trash bin'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "19": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "the cabinet under the rice maker",
          "the cabinet with a sponge",
          "the cabinet with a sink"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'cabinet under the rice maker'?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "In which direction of the bifold door is 'the cabinet with a sponge'?",
            "answer": "Opposite",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a chair next to 'the cabinet with a sink'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      },
      "13": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The wall cabinet with the range hood hanging",
          "The wall cabinet containing toilet paper",
          "The wall cabinet closest to the cutting board"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is 'The wall cabinet with the range hood hanging'",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What direction is 'The wall cabinet containing toilet paper' relative to the stove",
            "answer": "Directly above",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a refrigerator next to 'The wall cabinet closest to the cutting board'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "kettle": {
      "22": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The kettle in front of rice cooker",
          "The kettle next to the sink",
          "Kettle in white and black"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Consider the kettle in white and black, is it closer to rice maker or sink?",
            "answer": "Sink",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the kettle next to the sink'?",
            "answer": "White and black",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is above 'the kettle in front of rice maker'?",
            "answer": "Wall cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "trash can": {
      "38": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "trash bin under the cutting board",
          "trash bin closest to the stove",
          "gray trash bin"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'trash bin under the cutting board'",
            "answer": "Gray",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a table next to the 'trash bin closest to the stove'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Where is the 'gray trash bin' in relation to the stove",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "board": {
      "32": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Light wood color cutting board",
          "The cutting board closest to the bifold door",
          "The cutting board closest to the toilet paper"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'Light wood color cutting board'",
            "answer": "Cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'cutting board closest to the bifold door'",
            "answer": "Light wood color",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "In what direction from the toilet paper is the 'cutting board closest to the toilet paper'",
            "answer": "Below",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "box": {
      "10": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The box closest to the refrigerator",
          "The box under the table",
          "The box next to the black suitcase"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is 'the box closest to the refrigerator' red?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a pot next to 'the box under the table'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the position of 'the box next to the black suitcase' in relation to the table?",
            "answer": "Under",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "9": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Yellow polka dot suitcase",
          "The suitcase under the table",
          "The suitcase furthest from the rice cooker"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Where is the yellow polka dot suitcase in relation to the table?",
            "answer": "underneath",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Does 'The suitcase under the table' have a bird pattern on it",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is on top of 'the suitcase furthest from the rice cooker'",
            "answer": "table",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      },
      "36": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "black suitcase",
          "the suitcase closest to the sink",
          "the black suitcase next to the refrigerator"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Where is the 'black suitcase' in relation to the refrigerator?",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the suitcase closest to the sink' pink?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a book on 'the suitcase closest to the sink'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "stove": {
      "37": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White stove",
          "The stove next to the trash can",
          "The stove closest to the cutting board"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a pot on the 'White stove'",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'stove next to the trash can'",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a trash can near 'the stove closest to the cutting board'?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "door": {
      "5": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The white bifold door",
          "The bifold door on the floor",
          "The bifold door next to the white object"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "In which direction of the floor is the 'white bifold door'?",
            "answer": "Above",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is 'the bifold door on the floor'?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a sponge on 'the bifold door next to the white object'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "book": {
      "16": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "Books on top of the refrigerator",
          "Books closest to the ceiling",
          "Colorful books"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a kettle next to the 'Books on top of the refrigerator'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'Books closest to the ceiling'",
            "answer": "refrigerator",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Consider the books on top of the refrigerator, are they the same color as the suitcase below?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "faucet": {
      "34": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The water faucet above the sink",
          "The water faucet next to the sponge",
          "The water faucet near kettle"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Where is 'The water faucet above the sink' relative to the sponge",
            "answer": "next to",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'The water faucet next to the sponge' in the same color with the sponge?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "Is 'the water faucet near kettle' taller or shorter than the kettle?",
            "answer": "Shorter",
            "tag": "geometry",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "refrigerator": {
      "17": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White refrigerator",
          "Refrigerator under the book",
          "Refrigerator next to the black suitcase"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Where is the 'white refrigerator' in relation to the book",
            "answer": "Underneath",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'refrigerator under the book'",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a door next to the 'refrigerator next to the black suitcase'",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "range hood": {
      "14": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White range hood",
          "Range hood above the stove",
          "Range hood closest to the cutting board"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Where is the 'White range hood' relative to the stove?",
            "answer": "Above",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What color is the 'range hood above the stove'?",
            "answer": "White",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a sink next to the 'range hood closest to the cutting board'?",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "sink": {
      "29": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "sink under the water faucet",
          "sink next to the kettle",
          "sink closest to the refrigerator"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is the 'sink under the water faucet' red",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the position of the 'sink next to the kettle' in relation to the water faucet",
            "answer": "below",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is there a stove next to the 'sink closest to the refrigerator'\n",
            "answer": "No",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "table": {
      "8": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "The table next to the black suitcase",
          "The table closest to the refrigerator",
          "The table next to the chair"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Is there a door opposite the table next to the black suitcase?",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "existence",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          },
          {
            "question": "What is the position of the table closest to the refrigerator relative to the chair?",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the table next to the chair blue?",
            "answer": "No.",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    },
    "rice cooker": {
      "21": {
        "grounding_text": [
          "White rice cooker",
          "Rice cooker next to the kettle",
          "Rice cooker closest to the sponge"
        ],
        "qa": [
          {
            "question": "Where is the 'white rice cooker' located in relation to the kettle",
            "answer": "Beside",
            "tag": "spatial",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "Is the 'rice cooker next to the kettle' white?",
            "answer": "Yes",
            "tag": "appearance",
            "extra_knowledge": 0
          },
          {
            "question": "What is under the 'rice cooker closest to the sponge'?",
            "answer": "Cabinet",
            "tag": "class",
            "extra_knowledge": 1
          }
        ]
      }
    }
  }
}